# **Thomas J Lazore**

Software Developer

Address Savannah, GA, 31410

Phone 315-778-6632

E-mail tomlazore@gmail.com

Full stack software developer certified from Georgia Tech. Experience working with technologies such as JavaScript, Express, and MongoDB in the development of group and solo projects. An effective team member and resourceful independent worker due to leadership background as a paramedic.

#### **Projects**

# Never Alone | github.com/tlaze/NeverAlone

- Live Application: never-alone-platform.herokuapp.com/
- **Description:** Team of 4 members developing a social media website geared towards mental health. This project had a 50 person user base. Each were able to create personal profiles and add unique posts/comments.
- Responsibilities: Creating, editing, and deleting posts | Mobile Responsiveness.
- Technology Used: Bootstrap | Javascript | Node | Express | Handlebars | Express-Session | MySQL2 | Sequelize | bcrypt | Heroku | Nodemailer

# Tech Blog | github.com/tlaze/tech-blog

- Live Application: cryptic-thicket-49114.herokuapp.com/
- Description: Forum based application for creating posts, updating, and deleting posts.
- Technology Used: Bootstrap | Javascript | Node | Express | Handlebars | Express-Session | MySQL2 | Sequelize | bcrypt | Heroku

# Weather Dashboard | github.com/tlaze/weather-dashboard

- Live Application: tlaze.github.io/weather-dashboard/
- **Description:** Fetches data from a third party API to display current and future weather conditions for cities that users enter.
- Technology Used: HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Javascript | JQuery | OpenWeatherOneAPI | Local Storage

#### Education

# 2021-09 - 2021-12 Certificate: Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, GA

# 2011-09 - 2013-12 Associate of Applied Science: Fire Protection Technology

Monroe Community College - Rochester, NY

Relevant Coursework: Intro to Computer Science with Java & Programming with Python

#### **Work History**

# 2017-09 - 2020-03 Paramedic

Irondequoit Ambulance, Irondequoit, NY

- Triaged injuries by communicating with patients, bystanders and family members, and identified appropriate medical facility for transport.
- Used EMSCharts to accurately document services provided to reduce liability and improve patient care.

## 2019-05 - 2019-08

#### **Research Assistant Intern**

Rochester Institute Of Technology, Rochester, NY

- Presented technical research results to diverse audiences through written, visual and oral media.
- https://www.cs.rit.edu/~dprl/mathseer/